life is a journey full of possibilities
and every decision we make shapes our
future
we need to choose the path that leads to
more
Financial Security more wealth creation
and more value for money for a brighter
tomorrow
presenting ICICI Pro signature a
unit-linked life insurance plan that is
designed to give you more in every
aspect of your financial Journey
its numerous benefits make it an
incredible choice
unlock the potential of market-driven
returns wealth boosters to boost your
Investments
life cover to safeguard the financial
future of your family
return of Premium allocation charges to
save more
choice of four portfolio strategies
with a wide range of funds
enjoy policy benefits till the age of 99
with the whole life policy term
systematic withdrawal plans for regular
payouts
Top-Up option for additional savings and
tax benefits
so let's see how this plan works meet Mr
Akshay a 40 year old id professional he
wishes to create wealth by the age of
60. so he selects the ICICI proof
signature plan with a 20-year policy
term and pays a premium of 2 lakh rupees
per year for 10 years on maturity he
will receive Market linked returns to
fulfill his goals in case of his death
during the policy term akshay's family
or nominee will receive the life cover
ICICI proves signature a plan that helps
you achieve more